PROPHECY TIME
There is a dispute over a child.
You need to reconcile. There is need for a reconciliation.
It is true.
Sometimes, we don't know where our problem comes from.
We begin to ask God to bless us but sometimes, there are mountains somewhere
that are standing against us.
We may not see it as a problem but it is a mighty problem.
If this vision is not given to you, you will keep asking for a breakthrough.
There can be no breakthrough without this reconciliation.
Man of God, what you said about me is true.
Without this reconciliation, getting this girl, standing and coming out to say:
"I am the father", you cannot get it right in life.
Man of God, it is true.
Man of God, please help me. I want to get this baby back to my life.
Please help me, Man of God.
There was a time that they took you to a witch doctor.
Do you remember it?
It is true, Man of God.
You were looking for deliverance.
There was a time they gave you a handkerchief.
It is true.
Okay.
After your deliverance, you will get this child back.
And you will pay the woman and say: "Sorry". This woman will forgive you.
Now, you can start your life again.
Thank You, Jesus.
TESTIMONY TIME
After that prophecy and the man was delivered,
he went back to his country, and he was able to trace the lady.
SCOAN Sunday Service
Since fourteen years.
Let me tell you about deliverance.
Once they talk to you - one-on-one - that is deliverance.
Question and answer is what they provide.
My name is Frank Dagbe.
I come from Ghana.
Firstly, I want to thank the man of God immensely for allowing himself to be used by God Almighty
to dig out the root cause of my problems.
I was here in December 2008 for breakthrough, and the man of God saw me.
I was sitting here and he said I was looking for breakthrough
but there is a dispute over a child in my life.
I should go and reconcile and thank this woman immensely
before there would be breakthrough in my life.
Actually, that was done and as I'm here,
I can say that there is a total breakthrough in my life.
Before then, things weren't going well.
That was why I came here because I was watching Emmanuel TV
and I saw what God uses the man of God to do in people's lives.
He came here for breakthrough -
there was no job, no money.
I said: "Look, this is the problem you have.
This is the root of your problem.
Some years past, there was a woman you abandoned.
You said you don't know; you are a small boy.
You are the owner of the child."
I said: "Don't worry. After this deliverance, you will just see the whole thing,
and they too will be looking for you.
As you are looking for them, they will be looking for you.
If they now see you, they will say, "Thank You, Jesus! We've been looking for you!"
SCOAN Sunday Service
The man of God said that there is a dispute over a child.
Actually, before she was conceived, I denied her,
saying that I wasn't the one who impregnated her mother.
They came to meet my parents and then my father called me away from her parents
that I should accept it because he's also a man; he went through all
this when he was in school, that I should say the truth but I still denied it.
Clap for his father.
You see a good father.
His good father called him secretly and said: "Look, I'm a man.
What I'm seeing now, from the look of things, this pregnancy of three months -
you are the owner."
He said: "No, no, no!"
What the man of God said is nothing but the truth
because I never knew that that was the problem.
I even connived with one of my cousins to support me to deny her.
Glory be to God!
Look at the way God called me into his life.
He came from Ghana crying but the Lord said: "No, no, no!
That child of fourteen years ago you denied!
Go back and take the child. If not, you will be poorer than this".
I never knew that that was the problem.
Actually, I was looking for breakthrough.
I want to express my gratitude to the man of God for allowing himself
to be used immensely for my problem.
Now, after the prophecy, there is breakthrough in my life.
I've got a contract now. Even as I'm here, there was a phone call for me.
A contract is waiting for me in Ghana now.
Man of God, I thank you immensely for what God has used you to do in my life.
You have just started because I'm seeing you travel to Canada.
You should get ready.
Let's ask the little girl.
How are you feeling now,
now that you have discovered your father after fourteen years?
My name is Hilda Dagbe.
I am 14 years old.
I am happy to see my father now.
SCOAN Sunday Service
If not this message, this man would have denied forever.
The lady said I am happy now. After fourteen years, I am now able to know my father.
Man of God, I thank you.
I thank God for using you to tell my father
because when I'm in school, I've been seeing people's parents coming for them at school.
So, now I'm happy that I'm with my father.
SCOAN Sunday Service
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.
RV: PavelTatyanaZheleznyakov 17/06/2018